Federal Art Project, Photographic Division
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artist Files, circa 1920-1965, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-24; 9.6 linear feet)
  - Kantor, Joseph, 1937-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Kapfenberger, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Kaplan, Joseph, 1938-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Karfunkle, David, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 17)
    includes photos of Karfunkle, circa 1938
  - Karlan, Gertrude, 1937-1938, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Karlen, Agnes, 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Karp, Ben, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Karp, William, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 21)
    includes photos of Karp, September 1936, September 1938
  - Katz, Hyman William, 1938, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Katz, Nathaniel, 1937-1938, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Katzieff, Julius, 1938, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Kauffman, Andrene, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Kaufman, Edwin, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Kaz, Nathaniel, 1937-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Kelly, Albert Sumter, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Kelpe, Karl, circa 1936, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Kelpe, Paul, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Kempton, Martha Greta, 1937, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Kennedy, Simon, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Kerkam, Earl, 1937, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Kerwood, Venetia Drake, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Kessel, Dmitri, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Kibrick, 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 36)
  - King, Alexander, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 37)
  - King, Daisy Blanche, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 38)
  - King, Roy Elwood, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 39)
    includes photo of King, October 1936
  - Kleiban, Lucy, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Klein, Frank A., circa 1936-circa 1937, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Klein, Michael, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Kleinman, Gladys, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Klonis, Stewart, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Kloss, Gene, circa 1936, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Knaths, Karl, circa 1936, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Knight, Frederic, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 47)
  - Knotts, Benjamin, circa 1938-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 48)
    includes photo of Knotts, circa 1936
  - Koerner, Daniel, 1937-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Kollwitz, Käthe, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Konzal, Joseph, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Kopman, Benjamin, 1938-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Kopp, Beatrice, circa 1936, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Kormendi, Andre, 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Kotin, Albert, 1937-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Kovner, Saul, 1937-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Kozlow, Sigmund, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Kraus, Romuald, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 10)
    includes photos of Kraus, circa 1937
  - Krause, Erik Hans, 1936, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Kroll, Leon, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Kubinyi, Kalman, 1937, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 14)
    includes photos of Kuniyoshi, October 1940
  - Kurtz, 1939, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Lacher, Gisella Loeffler, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 16)
  - LaGrone, Oliver, circa 1935-circa 1942, circa 1958, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 17)
    includes photo of LaGrone
  - Lahey, Marguerite Dupuz, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 18)
  - La More, Chet, 1939, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Landeck, Armin, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Lane, Harry, 1939-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Laning, Edward, circa 1937-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 22)
    includes photos of Laning, 1937, 1938, 1940; see also Subject Files, Artists at Work, Box 25, F18
  - Laredo, Victor, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 23)
  - La Spina, N., 1941-1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Lassaw, Ibram, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Lassen, Ben, 1938-1939, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Laufman, Sidney, 1938-1940, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Laurent, Robert, 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Lauson, Michael, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Lawler, Paul, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Lawrence, Jacob, 1938, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Lawrence, William H., 1937-1938, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Lazzari, Pietro, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Lebduska, Lawrence H., circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Leboit, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Lechay, James, 1937-1938, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Lee, Doris, 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Leefe, Miriam, circa 1958, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Lehman, Harold, 1937-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Lenhard, Josef, 1937-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Lentelli, Leo, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Leurs, Golda, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Lever, Hayley, 1937, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Levi, Julian E., circa 1938-circa 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 44)
    includes photo of Levi, 1940 October
  - Levinson, Abraham F., 1938, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Levow, Irving, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Levy, D., 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 47)
  - Levy, Josephine Frankel, 1939, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 48)
    photo of Levy, April 1939
  - Levy, Martha, 1938-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 13 (hol), Folder 49)
  - Lewandowski, Edmund D., 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Monty, 1937-1938, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 2)
    includes photo of Lewis, 1938 May
  - Lewitts, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Liberte, Lewis Jean, 1937-1941, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Lieberman, William, 1937-1939, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Lightfoot, Elba, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 6)
    includes photo of Lightfoot, 1938 January
  - Liguori, Charles, 1937-1938, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Limarzi, Joseph, 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Limbach, Russell T., circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 9)
    includes photo of Limbach, 1938 January
  - Lindenthaler, Charles, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Lipshitz, Isadore, 1938-1940, (R: 1167) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Lishinsky, Abraham, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 12)
    includes photos of Lishinsky, circa 1939
  - Litchfield, Nell, 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Livingstone, Roland, 1939-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Locke, Charles, circa 1936, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Lockwood, Ward, 1935, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Loew, Michael, 1937-1939, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Lo Medico, Thomas, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 18)
    includes photos of Lo Medico, 1938 May
  - Lomoff, Joseph, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Lonergan, John, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Lonsbury, Earl, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Lo Pinto, Ferdinand, 1937-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Lord, Francisco P., circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 23)
    includes photos of Lord, 1938 August
  - Lorenz, Howard Taft, 1937-1938, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Louis, Morris (see Bernstein, Morris Louis), (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol))
  - Lowell, Nat, circa 1936-circa 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Lowengrund, Margaret, 1936-1937, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Lozowick, Louis, circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Luban, Boris, 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Lubin, Jacob, 1936-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Lubovsky, Maxim, 1937-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Luce, Molly, 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Lucioni, Luigi, 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Ludins, Ryah, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 33)
    includes photos of Ludins, 1937, 1939
  - Luisi, Nicholas, 1937-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Lunnon, James, circa 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Lurie, Nan, 1937-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Lush, Vivian R., circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1168) (Box 14 (hol), Folder 37)
  - MacAdams, Edgar, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Maccoy, Guy, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 2)
    includes photos of Maccoy and Leonard Jenkins, circa 1937
  - MacDonald, Julian, 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Magafan, Jennie, 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Mahl, Claire, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Maldarelli, Louis, 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Malderelli, Oronzio, 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Maloof, Sam, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Mandelman, Beatrice, 1939-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Manfredi, Joseph, 1937-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Mangor, E., circa 1936, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Manship, Paul, 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 12)
    photo of Manship
  - Marans, Moissaye, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 13)
    includes photo of Marans, circa 1939
  - Marcon, Julia, 1936-1937, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Marder, Ida, 1936-1938, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Margolis, David, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 16)
    includes photos of Margolis, 1949 May
  - Margoulies, Berta, 1939, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Mariinsky, Vaslav, 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Markham, Kyra (Kyle?), circa 1936-circa 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 19)
    includes photos of Markham, 1937 June
  - Markow, Jack, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Marshall, J., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Marshall, Margaret, 1939, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 22)
    photo of Marshall
  - Martin, Robert, 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Massa, Frederick, circa 1939-circa 1942, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Mastaglis, Dominico, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Matta, Santiago, circa 1939, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Mattei, Antionio, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Matulka, Jan, 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Matzal, Leopold Charles, 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Maunsbach, Eric, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Maxey, Stevens, 1937-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Mayer, Bena Frank, 1940-1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Mayer, Jules, 1937-1938, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 33)
  - McAuliffe, Florence, circa 1936, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 34)
  - McCown, Eugene, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 35)
  - McCoy, S., 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 36)
  - McCrady, John, 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 37)
  - McGirr, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 38)
  - MacIver, Loren, 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 39)
  - McKiernan, John, circa 1937, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 40)
  - McMahon, Audrey, circa 1938, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 41)
    includes photos of McMahon and Holger Cahill
  - McNeil, George J., 1937-1940, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 42)
  - McNulty, 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Means, Elliot, circa 1938-circa 1940, (R: 1168) (Box 15 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Mecklem, Austin, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Mecklin, Hannah, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Meert, Gertrude, circa 1936, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Meert, Joseph John Paul, circa 1936, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Meiere, Hildreth, circa 1940, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Melicov, Dina, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 6)
    includes photos of Melicov, 1938 February, 1939 April
  - Meloy, Henry J., 1937-1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Metaruga, 1937, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Meyer, George, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Meyer, Herbert, 1936-1940, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Michalsky, Maximilian, circa 1935-circa 1941, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Michnick, David, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Milavsky, B., 1941, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Miller, Barse, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Miller, Benjamin, 1937-1939, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Miller, Hugh, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Millman, Edward, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Mims, Thomas, circa 1936-circa 1937, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Mira, Alfred, 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Miserendino, Vincenzo, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Mitchell, Bruce, circa 1941, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Mitchell, Henry J., 1937, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Mock, 1936, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Mock, Gladys, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Moldovan, Sacha, 1937-1941, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Mommer, Paul, 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Montalbano, Charles, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Moore, William, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Moran, Eliza, 1939, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Morley, Eugene, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Morosoff, Vladimir, 1938-1939, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Morris, Carl A., 1940, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Morris, James, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Mose, Eric, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 34)
    includes photos of Mose, circa 1936-circa 1939
  - Mousseau, Roland, circa 1936, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Moylan, Lloyd, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Mues, William, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Mundhenk, Oscar, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Murphy, M. Lois, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Murray, Hester Miller, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Murrell, Sara, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Muschnik, D., circa 1936, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Myers, Jerome, circa 1937, (R: 1169) (Box 16 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Nadejena, Lydia, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1169) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Nagai, Thomas, 1937, 1941, (R: 1169) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Nagy, Frank, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 3)
    includes photos of Nagy, circa 1939
  - Nakagawa, Kikudo, circa 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Nakamizo, Fuji, circa 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Nakian, Reuben, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Nash, Ginerva, 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Nastasi, Frank, 1940, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Naumer, Helmuth, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Neagoe, Anna, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Neel, Alice, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Nelson, Bruce, 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Nelson, C. G., 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Nelson, Helen, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Nesin, George, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Neuwirth, Morris, circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Nevelson, Louise, circa 1939-circa 1940, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 17)
  - New, Babette, circa 1936-circa 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Newell, James Michael, circa 1936-circa 1941, (2 folders; R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 19-20)
    includes photos of Newell, circa 1937
  - Niberg, Abbey, circa 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Nickerson, J. Ruth, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Nicolosi, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Nisanoff, Louis, 1937-1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Niswonger, Ilse, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Noble, Carl E., circa 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Nooney, Ann, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Nordfeldt, B.J.O., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Norling, Ernest, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 29)
    includes photo of Norling, circa 1937
  - Norman, Geoffrey, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Novelli, James, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Nusbaum, Jesse, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Nye, Edgar, 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Oldfield, Otis William, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Olds, Elizabeth (see also Dehn, Adolf), circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 35)
    includes photos of Olds, 1937
  - Olenikov, S., circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Oley, Moses, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Opper, John, 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Owen, Robert Emmett, 1939, 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Owen, William, 1938-1941, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Paine, Elizabeth, 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Paleologue, Jean, 1938-1939, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Palmer, William C., circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 43)
    includes photos of Palmer, 1936-1937
  - Palter, Rebecca, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 17 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Pandolfini, Joseph, 1937-1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Paolo, C. S., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Parish, Betty Waldo, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Parsons, Sheldon, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Pattison, Carrie A., 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Pecci, Mario, 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Peck, Augustus, 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Pels, Albert, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Penney, John James, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Pereira, I. Rice, 1938-1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 10)
    includes photos of Pereira, 1938
  - Perelli, Victor, 1937-1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Peri, Eve, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Perper, Marc, 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Perry, circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Perry, Roland Hinton, 1936-1939, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Peterdi, Gabor, circa 1950, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Pettit, Grace, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Phillips, Bert, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Phillips, Elizabeth, 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Phillips, Robert, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Picus, Robert, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Pierce, Leona, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Pine, Geri, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Pinto, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Pittman, Hobson, 1940, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Pleissner, Ogden M., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Poirier, Emily, 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Pollock, Charles, 1940, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Pollock, Jackson, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Polowetski, Charles E., 1937-1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Pont, Charles Ernest, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Poole, Nelson, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Poor, Henry Varnum, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Poucher, Elizabeth Morris, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Powell, Arthur James Emery, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Powell, Leslie, circa 1937-circa 1945, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Preacher, 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Prestopino, Gregorio, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Pusterla, 1937, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Pytlak, Leonard, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Quackenbush, Paschal, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Quilter, Ernest, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Quirt, Walter, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Rabner, Tina, 1940-1942, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Raboy, Mac, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Racioppi, Angelo, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1170) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 46)
    includes photos of Racioppi
  - Ramer, Nat, 1937, (R: 1171) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 47)
  - Ransom, Fosden, circa 1941-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 48)
    includes photos of Ransom, 1942
  - Raskin, Joseph, 1937-1938, (R: 1171) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 49)
  - Ratzker, Max, 1939-1941, (R: 1171) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 50)
  - Raucher, David, 1940, (R: 1171) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 51)
  - Recke, Gerard, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1171) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 52)
  - Reeves, Ruth, circa 1939-circa 1940, (R: 1171) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 53)
    includes photos of Reeves, 1939-1940
  - Refregier, Anton, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1171; 2 folders) (Box 18 (hol), Folder 54-55)
    includes photos of Refregier, 1939
  - Reichman, Agatha, 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Rein, Harry, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Reina, Salvatore, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1171) (Box 19 (hol), Folder 3)
    includes photo of Reina, 1941